

PROFILE

Masterful Developer with proficiency in DEVELOPING Front End UI.

I am currently working for Capgemini, as a developer. I have 1.6 years of experience as a developer and love working with React and other hip frameworks. I design and code simple things, and I love what I do.

My work experience has given me the knowledge and skills to quickly adapt to changing circumstances and continue achieving the best performance.

PHONE:

+91 8092766575

shubham14p3@gmail.com

Hyperlinks:

- PORTFOLIO
- HACKERRANK
- GITHUB
- LINKEDIN

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Critical Thinking

AWARDS

- Best employer of the year
- Techfest coder

PERSONAL INFO

Address:

H. No-21, Radha Kunj, Jyoti Nagar,Radhika Nagar, Kharangajhar, Telco,Jamshedpur, Jharkhand, India - 831004

SHUBHAM RAJ

SKILLS

Front-End: JavaScript, React, HTML5, CSS3, SASS

Tools & Methods: Git, GitHub, Heroku, Netlify, Bitbucket, Gitlab

Professional: Remote Pair-Programming, Teamwork

EXPERIENCE

Associate Consultant

Capgemini, Kolkata from 05-2021

Payroll: Capgemini

• Currently under training.

Solution Engineer

Gammastack, Indore 05-2020 – 08-2020

Payroll: Grep Ruby Webtech Pvt. Ltd., Indore

- Developed code to convert design wire-frames into website elements under supervision.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Worked in debugging codes to improve website performance and user experience.
- Worked within an agile team and helped prioritize and scope feature requests.

Trainee

Nagravision India Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore

07-2018 - 07-2019

Payroll: Alp Consulting Ltd., Bangalore

- Developed test cases and scripts using JavaScript.
- Developed a Defects Tracking Log for the SharePoint Site to track defects while testing.
- Gained hands-on expertise in Bootstrap, JavaScript and as well as frontend technologies like React
- Used Quality Center to store all testing results, metrics, created Test Cases, and Reporting.

EDUCATION

Microverse

Remote Full Stack Web Development Program

2019 -- 2020

- Spent 1300+ hours mastering algorithms, data structures, and full-stack development while simultaneously developing projects with Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, React, and Redux.
- Developed skills in remote pair-programming using GitHub, industrystandard gitflow, and daily standups to communicate and collaborate with international remote developers

Bhilai Institute of Technology

Bachelor in Engineering with Computer Science Engineering 2014-2018

- Followed my passion in Software Development and completed Bachelor Engineering in Computer Science & Engineering.
- Represented my College in many national and domestic events.

Vidya Bharati Chinmaya Vidyalaya

10 + 2 with Science

2001 - 2014

 President of the school, facilitated monthly meetings to enhance a diverse community. Managed activities like monthly talks, workshops, and student panels.